blueservo.net 2013-04-06

# BlueServo

## BlueServo Privacy Policy

Your privacy is our top concern. We work hard to earn and keep your trust, so we adhere to the following principles to protect your privacy: 

  * We will never rent or sell your personally identifiable information to third parties for marketing purposes. 
  * We will never share your contact information with another user without your consent. 
  * Any personally identifiable information that you provide will be secured with all industry standard protocols and technology. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here or by means of a notice on our home page. If you continue to use the BlueServo service after notice of changes have been sent to you or published on our site, you hereby provide your consent to the changed practices. Please read this privacy policy to learn more about: 

  1. What personally identifiable information of yours is collected by BlueServo. 
  2. How the information is used. 
  3. With whom the information may be shared. 
  4. How you can access and change your Account information. 
  5. How to contact us. 

* * *

**1\. Personal Information Collected**  
We collect your personal information in the following ways: 

_Registration_  
In order to become a BlueServo user, you must first create an account on this web site. To create an account you are required to provide the following contact information: name, and email address, and a password chosen by you. 

_Cookies_  
Like most web sites, BlueServo uses cookies and web log files to track site usage. A cookie is a tiny data file which resides on your computer which allows BlueServo to recognize you as a user when you return to our site using the same computer and web browser. Unfortunately, if your browser settings do not allow cookies, you will not be able to use our website. Like the information you enter at registration or in your Profile, cookie and log file data is used to customize your experience on the web site. 

Additionally, if you log out of the BlueServo site you will need to re-enter your password the next time you visit in order to log in to your account. Another type of cookie, called a "session" cookie, is used to identify a particular visit to the BlueServo site. Session cookies expire after a short time or when you close your web browser. 

We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends. In the course of serving advertisements or optimizing services to our users, we may allow authorized third parties to place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. Any information provided to third parties through such cookies will not be personally identifiable but may provide general segment information, e.g. your industry or geographic location, for greater customization of your user experience, Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Unfortunately, if your browser settings do not allow cookies or you opt to refuse all cookies, you may not be able to use our website or services. BlueServo does not store personally identifiable information in the cookies. 

_Web Beacons_

We allow other companies, called ad networks, to serve advertisements to BlueServo users. Ad networks include third party ad servers, ad agencies, ad technology vendors and research firms. BlueServo may "target"some ads to users that fit a certain general profile - for example, "product managers in Texas." 

To deliver these ads properly, BlueServo may include a file, called a web beacon, from these ad networks within pages served by BlueServo so the networks may provide anonymized, aggregated auditing, research and reporting for advertisers as well as to target ads to you while you visit other websites. 

Because your web browser must request these advertisements and web beacons from the ad network's servers, these companies can view, edit or set their own cookies, just as if you had requested a web page from their site. 

These general targets may also be used by ad networks to display targeted ads on other websites as a substitute for random, irrelevant ads. BlueServo never provides personally identifiable information to any advertiser nor any third party. 

_Log files, IP addresses and information about your computer_

Due to the communications standards on the Internet, when you visit the BlueServo web site we automatically receive the URL of the site from which you came and the site to which you are going when you leave BlueServo. We also receive the Internet protocol (IP) address of your computer (or the proxy server you use to access the World Wide Web), your computer operating system and type of web browser you are using, email patterns, as well as the name of your ISP. This information is used to analyze overall trends to help us improve the BlueServo service. The linkage between your IP address and your personally identifiable information is never shared with third-parties without your permission or except when required by law. 

**2\. Uses of personal information**

_BlueServo Communications_

BlueServo will communicate with you through email and notices posted on this website. Please be aware that you will always receive certain emails from BlueServo related to the proper functioning of your account. BlueServo may send you promotional information unless you have opted out of receiving such information 

Other information, that does not personally identify you as an individual, is collected by BlueServo Corporation from BlueServo users (such as, by way of example, patterns of utilization) and is exclusively owned by BlueServo. This information can be utilized by BlueServo in such manner as BlueServo, in its sole discretion, deems appropriate. 

_Sharing Information With Third Parties_

BlueServo takes the privacy of our users very seriously. We will never sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personally identifiable information to any third parties for marketing purposes. We will only share your personally identifiable with third parties to carry out your instructions and to provide specific services or information. These third parties do not retain, share, or store any personally identifiable information except to provide these services and are bound by strict confidentiality agreements which limit their use of such information. 

We may provide aggregated anonymous data about the usage of our services to third-parties for such purposes as we deem, in our sole discretion, to be appropriate, including, without limitation, to prospective advertisers on BlueServo. We may segment our users by role. If you would like to be excluded from the aggregated research or products based upon aggregated data about our users' activities on the site, please email [info@BlueServo.com](mailto:info@blueservo.com). 

_Teaming with Other Organizations to Offer Combined and Other Services_

BlueServo may offer our services in connection with other web sites (including updates about the BlueServo service) or may team with other online services to give you the combined results of both services or additional services and benefits. 

_Surveys and Polls_

As a member of BlueServo you will receive requests to participate in market research including polls and surveys submitted by other BlueServo members. If you participate in surveys and polls offered through the service, the information you provide may be visible to others using the service. 

_Legal Disclaimer_

It is possible that we may need to disclose personal information when required by law. We will disclose such information wherein we have a good-faith belief that it is necessary to comply with a court order, ongoing judicial proceeding, or other legal process served on our company or to exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. 

_Disclosures to others_

We may also disclose your personal and other information you provide, to another third party as part of a reorganization or a sale of the assets of a BlueServo corporation division or company and only after taking steps to ensure that your privacy rights continue to be protected. Any third party to which we transfer or sell BlueServo's assets will have the right to continue to use the personal and other information that you provide to us. 

**3\. Your Information Choices**

_Accessing and Changing Your Account Information_

You can review the personal information you provided us and make any desired changes to the information you publish, or to the settings for your BlueServo account including your email, and contact preferences, at any time by logging in to your account on the BlueServo website. Please be aware that even after your request for a change is processed, BlueServo may for a time retain residual information about you in its backup and/or archival copies of its database. 

You can also close your account through the BlueServo website. If you close your BlueServo account, we will remove your name and other personally identifiable information. We may retain certain data if it may be necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, or for legitimate business purposes, such as analysis of aggregated, non-personally-identifiable data, account recovery, or if required by law. All retained data will continue to be subject to the terms of the BlueServo Privacy Policy in effect at the time of your request. To request that we close your account and remove your information from the BlueServo service, please send your request to [info@BlueServo.com](mailto:info@blueservo.com). Please send your request using an email account that you have registered with BlueServo under your name. 

**Important Information**

_Children_

Children are not eligible to use our service and we ask that minors (under the age of 18) do not submit any personal information to us or use the service. 

If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact BlueServo by email at [info@BlueServo.com](mailto:info@blueservo.com). 

_Changes to this Privacy Policy_

BlueServo may update this privacy policy at any time. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account. 

If you continue to use the BlueServo service after notice of changes have been sent to you or published on our site, you hereby provide your consent to the changed practices. 

**4\. How to contact us**

If you have questions or comments about this privacy policy, please email us at [info@BlueServo.com](mailto:info@blueservo.com). 

Last updated on November 2, 2008
